The Byzel Fight Festival that
Meliodas and Co. entered to retrieve
(ﾅﾚｰｼｮﾝ)＜ディアンヌの神器を
手にすべく参加した喧嘩祭りも➡
いよいよ 決勝戦＞
Diane's Sacred Treasure
finally enters the last round.
＜ディアンヌ対メリオダス＞
Diane versus Meliodas!
Who will be the one
＜果たして どちらが勝つのか＞
to win this battle?
You...
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)この…｡
(ﾒﾘｵﾀﾞｽ)ん？
Hmm?
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)浮気者～～‼
ドゴン！
cheater!
Meanwhile, Guila's group of
Holy Knights closes in on them.
＜更に
ギーラたち聖騎士の一団が迫る＞
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
I continue to take everything in my arms
subete o daite koko ni irun da
For that's where our light lies
hikari wa soko ni aru yo
With unyielding emotions in tow,
yuzurenai omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me to you
yume o tsunaida kimi to
A beginning will someday be born from our own hands
hajimari o itsuka bokura no te de umidasun da yo
And with how kind you are, I'm sure your voice will be able to change the world
yasashii kimi no koe mo kitto sekai o kaerareru
Since people can't totally stand up all on their own,
dare mo hitori kiri ja tachiagare yashinai kara
we'll reach out our hands to one another
tagai ni te o nobashite
and head for a tomorrow that surpasses all limits
kagiri no koeta ashita e
I'll shout out a love that doesn't cease to resound
nariyamanu ai o sakebu yo
As we begin to butt heads and get to know one another better,
butsukariatte wakariaun da
we'll create a path of light.
hikari o tsukuridasu yo
Guided by my tenacity,
akiramenu omoi o kakete
I'll be the one to live on the edge of my hopes
kibou no hate o boku wa ikiru yo
A dream connects me with you
yume o tsunai da kimi to
Episode 12
Terrifying Cannon
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)マトローナ
開始早々 強烈な先制～！
Matrona delivers a vicious preemptive strike!
I'm not showing you any mercy after all that's gone on today!
今日という今日は
許さないんだから～！
さっきのは誤解だ｡
俺には 全く覚えが…｡
Wait, you're just misunderstanding something.
I don't remember—
言い訳無用だ～い！
I don't wanna hear your excuses!
こりゃ
本気でやらなきゃ やばいかも！
I actually have to take this seriously, or else I'll be—
んんっ！
ドン ドン ドン… ドォーン！
Hey, is the stage going to even hold until the fight is over?
おい この会場 もつのかよ…｡
ほっ ううっ… んん！
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)はあ～ おりゃあ！
痛ぇだろ！
んにゃ！
That hurts!
Stupid Captain!
団長のばか～～！
ドゴン！
What happened?
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)どうした？ あっ｡➡
ん？
(ｹｲﾝ)これは…｡
Huh?
This is...
What's going on?
(観客)どうしちまったんだ？
(観客)これで終わりか？
Is this how it all ends?
Don't just stand there!
(観客)いつまで待たせんだ！
(観客)さっさと始めろ！
Keep fighting!
(ﾎｰｸ)あの二人
さては 力み過ぎて漏らしたな？
Did they stress out too much and piss themselves?
Lord Ban? Lord King?
(ｴﾘｻﾞﾍﾞｽ)バン様？ キング様？
俺の正体は 七つの大罪 団長➡
My true indentity is the Captain of the Seven Deadly Sins,
憤怒の罪のメリオダスだ！
The Dragon's Sin of Wrath, Meliodas!
We'll be taking over the town of Byzel now!
このバイゼルは
そっくり丸ごと 俺たちが頂く！
Eh? What's going on?!
えっ 何？ あのバカ➡
Why did those idiots reveal their true identity?
なんで 正体バラしちゃってんの？
Right, Elizabeth? What do
you think they're planning?
ねえ エリザベスちゃん なんで!?
I'll give you all one minute
to get your asses out of Byzel!
あと１分以内に
このバイゼルの町から消えうせろ｡
さもなきゃ 全員 皆殺しにする！
Or else, we will massacre every last one of you!
何ぬかしてんだ このガキ！
手配書とは 全然違うじゃねぇか！
What the hell are you saying, you brat?!
You don't look anything like the wanted poster!
おい でも
あいつらの強さ もしかして…｡
Yeah, but you saw how strong they are.
Could it be...?
Wh-What's suddenly gotten into the four of them?
(心の声)≪よ… 四人とも
急に どうしてしまったの？≫
とっとと うせろ～‼
Get the hell out of here!
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)ひゃあ～！
あっ… おい あれ！
Hey, look at that!
ドカーン！
ドカン！ ドカン！ ドカン！
キン！
Full Counter
ちぇっ！ もう来たか｡
They're here already.
Their equipment is on par with our Sacred Treasures.
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)あの装備 神器クラスだぞ｡
I'll bet they're incomparably stronger
than Guila back at the Capital of the Dead.
おそらく
死者の都のときのギーラとは➡
比較にならねぇ強さのはずだ｡
何より 今度の相手は 三人｡
And this time, we're up against three.
Let's split up for now!
ひとまず散るぞ｡
Get out of the town! Hurry!
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)町の外へ出ろ！ 急げ！
Follow that man over there!
(ｹｲﾝ)あの男の後に ついてゆけ！
Ellie? Ellie?!
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)エリー エリー！
あいつらめ 聞いていた予定より
全然早いじゃないか｡
Those bastards, this is earlier than we planned!
まだ エリーを
見つけていないってのに…｡
We haven't even found Ellie yet.
Princess Veronica.
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)ベロニカ様 ここは一旦➡
We should get away from here. The flames are too strong.
引き揚げましょう｡ 火の手が強い｡
No. If we pass up this chance,
ダメだ｡ この機会を逃したら➡
エリーを
永久に連れ戻せなくなる｡
we'll never be able to bring Ellie back.
Ellie?!
エリー！
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)お待ちください ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ様！
Please wait! Princess Veronica!
ヒュ～(口笛)
(ﾊﾞﾝ)派手にやってくれるねぇ｡➡
They sure like being flashy.
ん？
ドスッ！
ドゴッ！
ぐはっ！
I've been waiting to meet you for a long time.
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)お前に ずっと会いたかった｡
苦しいか？
Does it hurt?
Now this is what I call a festival!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)やっぱ
祭りは こうでなくっちゃなぁ｡
って お前 どっかで会ったっけ？
Wait, have we met before?
俺は ジェリコ｡
貴様に 辱めを受けた➡
I'm Jericho.
The Holy Knight apprentice you humiliated back at Baste. Do you remember now?
バステの聖騎士見習いと言えば
分かるか？
Oh, that barber boy?
あの散髪屋の坊主か｡
つぅか お前 女装趣味だったの？
Wait, you're into cross-dressing?
くっ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ぐわっ！
Godspeed: Cross Slash!
Godspeed: Cross Slash
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)｢神速之十閃｣！
ドォーン！
おいおい マジかよ…｡
Hey, hey, you've gotta be kidding me!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)≪血が… 傷が塞がらねぇ≫
The blood... won't stop flowing out.
The reason I pretended to be a man
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)
俺が 男のふりをしていたのは➡
was because I was weak, so I wanted to
make myself feel tougher any way I could.
弱い自分を 少しでも
強く見せようとしていたからだ｡
ガッ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ぐはっ！
But now, that is no longer needed.
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)だが もう その必要はない｡
My rage against you has
helped me reach a new level.
お前への怒りが
俺を 新たなステージに導いた｡
You've made me into a woman.
お前が 俺を女にした｡
この責任は取ってもらうぞ バン｡
I'll have you take full responsibility for me.
Ban.
It's been a while. Meliodas.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)お久しぶりです メリオダス｡
よう ギーラ｡
今日は なんの用だ？
Yo, Guila. What're you after today?
The events at the Capital of the Dead a while back were very instructive.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)死者の都では
大変 勉強になりました｡➡
今日は
その復習を兼ねて参じました｡
I'm here today for the follow-up class.
By follow-up class, you mean
you're just here for revenge, huh?
復習っつっても
リベンジの方の復讐だろ？
まあいいや 相手してやる｡
It doesn't really matter. I'll fight you.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)いいえ｡
もはや 相手にはなりません｡
No. At this point, it won't even be a fight anymore.
If I make a wrong move and touch
one of them, they'll explode, right?
下手に動いて触れたら
爆発を起こすってとこか｡
面倒だけど
片っ端から消していくか｡
It's annoying, but I guess I'll have to get rid of all of them!
お気を遣わずとも
勝手に爆発しますから｡
I'd be careful if I were you.
They'll explode on their own.
うわっ！
その１つ目の爆発を きっかけに➡
The first explosion will trigger a chain reaction of continuous explosions.
次々と連鎖が始まり➡
It'll trap the target in a cage of inferno.
標的を 爆炎の檻に閉じ込める｡
ドドォーーン！
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)｢ﾁｪｲﾝ･ｴｸｽﾌﾟﾛｰｼﾞｮﾝ｣！
Chain Explosion!
Chain Explosion
とんとことことこ
とんとことことこ！
焼き豚になろうと
豚串になろうと…➡
Whether I turn into grilled pork or pork kebab...
いや 豚足だけになろうと➡
Even if all that's left of me is pigs' feet...
必ず エリザベスちゃんを
守ってみせるぜ！
This time, I'll protect Elizabeth no matter what!
I won't let that happen!
そんなことは許しません！
へっ？
みんなで
無事に切り抜けるの｡ ねっ？
We're all going to get through this together. Okay?
Elizabeth!
エリザベスちゅわ～ん！ あっ｡
Lord Meliodas! Lord Ban!
メリオダス様！ バン様！
ドーン！
Are you just about done, Jericho?
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)ジェリコも終わったの？
どうしたの？ その唇｡
What happened to your lips?
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)ふっ｡
準備運動で終わってしまった｡
I was just getting warmed up and it's over already.
Delivering the coup de grâce to a Sin is just a perk of this mission.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)七つの大罪の始末は
あくまで 任務のおまけ｡➡
それに 最も注意すべき敵は
まだ残ってるわ｡
Besides, the main enemy we
need to be wary of is still around.
≪(ｷﾝｸﾞ)お～い 団長！➡
Hey, Captain!
みんな 無事 避難したみたいだよ｡
Everyone's done evacuating!
ん？ 団長！ バン！
Captain? Ban?
Crap!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)しまった～！
ドオォーーン！
なんちゃって｡
Just kidding.
Ah!
ガン！
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)ぐあぁ～！
はあっ！
パチン
さてと
準備運動も終わったことだし➡
Well then, now that we've
warmed up, why don't we—
そろそろ… あれ？
Oh?
Done already?
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)もうおしまい？
やるなぁ キング！
Good going, King!
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)まだ死んじゃいないさ｡➡
They're not dead yet.
彼女たちには
聞きたいこともあるし➡
I have a few questions for them.
団長たちを よろしく頼むよ｡
合点でい！
I'll leave Captain and the others to you.
Understood.
プッゴ～！
キング様も お気をつけて｡
Please be careful, Lord King!
Well then, what are you really after?
さてと
君たちの 本当のねらいは何かな？
(ﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾇ)ない！
ない ない な～い！
No, it's not here! It's gone!
僕のギデオンがな～い！
あ～ん どうしよう…｡
My Gideon is gone! What should I do?
This is bad! He was caught in Guila's explosion!
た… 大変！
ギーラの爆発に巻き込まれたんだ｡
The Serpent's Sin, Diane of the Seven Deadly Sins!
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)七つの大罪
嫉妬の罪 ディアンヌ！➡
That's as far as you go!
そこまでだ！
あっ ハウザー｡
Hauser?
For your crime ten years ago of assassinating the Great Holy Knight
１０年前の聖騎士長殺害と
王国転覆を謀った 反逆の罪で…｡
and attempting to overthrow the kingdom—
やってないよ？
ああっ？
I didn't do it...
This is more important.
それより
今はこっち｡ しっかりして｡
Hold on.
すぐ
安全な所に連れていくからね｡
I'll get you to safety right away.
ありがとう｡
ったく… 調子狂うぜ｡
Thank you.
Jeez, you're so unpredictable!
Hey! If y'all are in a pickle, lemme lend ya a hand.
(ﾏﾙﾏｽ)おい～っす｡
てこずってるなら手伝うべ｡➡
ドン ドン！ チャッ チャッ！➡
Don-don-cha-don,
ドン！ チャッ チャッ！ チャ～！
don-cha-cha!
ううっ！ うぅ…｡
ぐはっ！ 何… これ？➡
What's this? My body feels so heavy...
体が重い…｡
受け止めて ハウザー！
(ﾊｳｻﾞｰ)あっ？ っと…｡
Catch, Hauser!
Okay!
きゃあ～～！
ディアンヌ！
Diane!
プゴ～… プゴ～…｡
でえぇ～！ ああ～ しんど｡
Man, I'm beat!
ん？ エリザベスちゃん？
Elizabeth?
Please... Protect Lord Meliodas.
どうか
メリオダス様を お守りください｡
Elizabeth...
エリザベスちゃん…｡ ん？
エリザベスちゃん
大きくなってね？
Elizabeth, haven't you gotten a little bigger?
あっ！ た… 大変！
O-Oh no! My body is returning to normal!
体が 元の大きさに…｡
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)
どこにいるんだい？ あの子は｡
Where the hell is that girl?
They may not have come to this town.
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)この町には
来ていないのかもしれません｡
You expect me to ignore the plight of
a girl who's been taken advantage of?
これから利用しようって子を
わざわざ 一人にしておくかい？
I'm sure she's in this town somewhere.
きっと
この町の どこかにいるんだよ｡
Damn those Seven Deadly Sins!
おのれ 七つの大罪｡
≫きゃあ！
あっ｡
あっ エリー！
Ellie?
Veronica... My sister?
ベロニカ… 姉様？
姉様？
Sister?
あ… ありがとう ベロニカ姉様｡
Th-Thank you, Veronica.
ちょっと
下が スースーするけど…｡
There's a bit of a draft, though...
ったく
何が一体どうなってるんだい｡
Goodness, what in the world is going on?
はぁ…
でも 元気そうだね エリー｡
At least you look well, Ellie.
まっ あんたのことだから
無事でやってるとは思ったけどさ｡
Well, I should've known you'd be fine all along.
ベロニカ姉様…｡
Veronica...
What the hell do you think you're doing? Stupid Ellie.
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)なんて言うと思うか
バカエリー！➡
私を どれだけ
心配させるつもりなんだよ！
Do you have any idea how
much you made me worry?!
This is way more out of line than
sneaking out of the castle when we were kids!
子供のころ 城を抜け出して
遊んだときとは 訳が違うんだよ!?
あのときだって 橋が落ちて
大変だったじゃないか｡
Back then, when the bridge fell... That was already a big deal!
I-I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい｡
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)それに➡
Moreover, are you and the Seven Deadly Sins really hunting down Holy Knights, as the rumors say?
噂じゃ 七つの大罪と 聖騎士狩りを
しているそうじゃないか｡
No, that's a misunderstanding!
それは誤解です！
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)何が誤解なもんか！➡
What's there to misunderstand?
Aren't you with the Seven Deadly Sins right now?
現に 今も
七つの大罪と一緒じゃないか｡➡
仮にも 王国を
転覆させようとした連中だよ!?
They committed the deplorable act
of trying to overthrow the kingdom!
That's...
それは…｡
特に そのメリオダス！
Especially the one called Meliodas!
こいつの正体は
破壊の限りを尽くす➡
His true identity is a monster that brings only destruction!
化け物なんだよ！
あっ…｡
See, something came to mind, didn't it?
ほら 思い当たる節がある｡
Lord Meliodas is not a monster!
Nor has he brought about any destruction.
メリオダス様は
化け物でもないし➡
そんな非道を行うことは
ありません｡
もういい｡ こんなとこで
話をしていてもしかたない｡
I'm done.
There's no point in arguing here.
城へ帰るよ｡
嫌っ！ 放して！
Let's go back to the castle.
No, let go of me!
パシン！
くっ！
エリザベスは 俺が守る｡
メリオダス様｡
I'll be the one to protect Elizabeth.
Lord Meliodas!
Even at the cost of my life!
この命に代えて！
It's just as Hendriksen said...
ヘンドリクセンの言ったとおりだ｡
あんたが➡
Looks like you really did brainwash Ellie.
エリーを洗脳してるってのは
本当みたいだね｡
That's the "Goddess Amber."
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ･回想)
((それは ｢女神の琥魄｣｡➡
周囲 数フィート内の
魔の者のみに作用する➡
It only affects demonic beings within a small radius. It's very convenient.
便利な代物です｡➡
Please take that with you and get it near Meliodas.
それを持って
メリオダスに接近してください))
But carrying around something like that...
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)
((しかし そのようなもの➡
ベロニカ様に
危険が及ぶ可能性も…))
That would put Princess Veronica in danger as well!
Griamor, just like your father Dreyfus, you're too conservative.
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)((グリアモール
君は 父上のドレファスに似て➡
保守的すぎる))
((くっ…))
The target is a terrible criminal who poses a grave threat to the kingdom.
((相手は 王国に仇なす大罪人だ))
((早急に 手を打たねばならん))
We must act first.
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)((妹のためなら
なんだってやるよ))
I will do whatever it takes, if it's for my sister.
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)((ベロニカ様！))
Princess Veronica!
(ﾍﾝﾄﾞﾘｸｾﾝ)((エリザベス姫を
救えるのは あなただけです))
You're the only one who
can save Princess Elizabeth.
So, how exactly do I use this?
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)
((それで？ どうすればいい？))
When you're near Meliodas, recite this chant:
((メリオダスが そばにいるとき
こう唱えてください))
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)ロスコ･バスラ… メルシト｡
Rosco... Basra... Melcito...
Lord Meliodas?
メリオダス様… どこ？
Where'd he go?
い い… 石っころん中に？
えっ？
He got sucked into that rock?!
メリオダスは
本当に化け物だったんだ｡
So Meliodas really was a monster!
この石は 魔の者だけに反応し
封じる力があるんだ｡
This stone is only capable of
sealing away demonic beings!
What do you say? Have you snapped out of it now?
どうだい？
これで 目が覚めたろ！
メリオダス様を 元に戻して！
Bring Lord Meliodas back to the way he was before!
I don't how to do that.
戻す方法なんて知らないね｡
あっ｡
I hate you, Veronica! You don't even know anything about Lord Meliodas!
ベロニカ姉様なんて嫌いよ！
メリオダス様のこと
なんにも知らないくせに！
Griamor!
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)グリアモール！
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)はっ｡
Understood.
Perfect Shell
あっ！
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)｢完全なる独房｣｡➡
Perfect Shell!
There's no choice.
やむをえません｡
このまま 王国へ お連れします｡
We'll return you to the kingdom like this.
何を～！ こんな玉ころごとき➡
What did you say?! I'll bust open this lousy ball with my feet!
俺の豚足が ぶち破ったる｡ おりゃ！
ホークちゃん！
Hawk!
My wall is strong enough to survive even a meteor from outer space.
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)
俺の｢障壁｣は 地上へ降り注ぐ➡
星くずですら 破壊は不可能｡
≪(ﾊﾞﾝ)そんなら
俺は 腕１本で破ってやるかな｡
Maybe I'll crack it open with just an arm.
Actually, scratching it with a finger should be enough.
いいや 指１本で かき切れるか｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)≪妙だな｡ さっきから
団長とディアンヌの魔力が➡
Strange...
I haven't felt Captain's or Diane's power for a while now.
感じられない｡
バンの魔力も減り続けてるし…≫
Ban's power seems to be declining as well.
What's the matter? You don't look so well,
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)どうしました？ 顔色が
優れませんよ 妖精王 キング｡
Fairy King.
What did you do to Captain and Diane? And Ban, while we're at it.
団長とディアンヌに 何をしたの？
ついでに バンも｡
Never mind. I'll just go see for myself.
まあいっか 自分で確かめるよ｡➡
Oh, one last thing.
Next time you get in my way, I'll—
ああ～ あと 言っとくけど
君たち おいらの邪魔をしたら…｡
ふっ！
ドォーーン！
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)人の話は 最後まで聞こうよ｡
(２人)あっ｡
You should wait until people are finished talking.
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)一瞬で あの上空に!?
How did he get that high so quickly?!
Next time you get in my way, I'll finish you.
おいらの邪魔をしたら
今度は しとめる｡
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)
霊槍シャスティフォル 第四形態➡
Spirit Spear Chastiefol.
Form Four!
Sunflower
｢光華｣！
(２人)あっ！
Sunflower!
You two certainly were strong.
確かに 君たちは かなりの強さだ｡
もうあと１００年修業すれば
いい線いくんじゃない？
You might've amounted to something if you had trained for another 100 years.
ザシュ！
何!?
What?
My Chastiefol... Who did this?!
おいらのシャスティフォルを…
一体 誰が!?
Whoa, Old Fart is at a loss as to who foiled his signature move!
≪(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)お～っと おっさん
必殺の一撃を破られ 困惑必至～！
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)喧嘩祭りの審判!?
(ﾗﾌﾞﾍﾙﾑ)喧嘩祭りでの戦いが➡
The referee from before?
Did he have energy left over from the Fight Festival?!
消化不良だったのか
大人気ない おっさんの猛攻に➡
The Holy Knights Guila and Jericho were instantly killed by a merciless, ferocious attack from Old Fart!
ギーラ＆ジェリコの
両聖騎士 死亡～… は➡
But that would be a problem, so...
ちょっち困るので… はい！➡
Their savior is I, Love♡Helm!
助っ人は
俺っち ラブヘルムでした！➡
And his true identity is...!
そして その正体は…｡
はっ！
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)そ… そんな…｡
お前は ヘルブラム！
Th-That's—? You're—?!
Helbram?
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
いよぉ 久しぶり ハーレクイン｡➡
Yo! Long time, no see, Harlequin. Or should I say "King," as that is what you go by now?
いや 今は キングだっけ？
How are you alive?
なぜ生きている？
君は あのとき 確かに…｡
Back then, you definitely...
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
どうでもいい｡ もう昔の話だ｡
That doesn't matter. It's a thing of the past.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)ヘルブラム卿
私たちも加勢いたします｡
Lord Helbram, let us assist you!
No, that's fine. I'll be okay.
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)いや 結構 結構｡➡
俺っちが
キングを足止めする間に➡
While I keep King busy,
can you two go recover the target?
チミらは 例の目的物の回収に
行ってちょうだい｡
Yes, Sir!
はっ！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)さて… ん？➡
And now...
どうした？
緊張してるようだな｡➡
What's wrong? You look nervous.
Such a coward. You haven't changed a bit.
小心者のお前らしいよ｡
ふん… 本気で おいらを
一人で足止めできると思うのか？
Do you really think you can hold me back by yourself?
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
さすが 神樹から作った霊槍｡➡
Of course, a Spirit Spear forged from the Sacred Tree
真っ二つに折ったくらいじゃ
すぐ再生するわな｡
will regenerate in no time, even if it's split in two.
ドカッ！
(ｷﾝｸﾞ)ううっ… くっ！
ゴン！
うわっ！ ぐはっ…｡
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)もう息切れか？ 王様｡➡
Out of breath already, your highness?
魔力に反比例して
体力は ほんと 人並み以下だな｡
Your stamina is below the level of humans, much unlike your powers.
くっ！
ガン！
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)おっとっと…｡➡
Oops...
What's this? So you do have some fight left in you.
なんだよ｡ まだ 一応
やる気はあるんじゃないの｡➡
Now, why don't we enjoy the festival some more,
さあ もっと
祭りを楽しもうじゃないか➡
古き友よ｡
my old friend.
Y-You bastard!
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)き… 貴様
ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ様から その汚い手を放せ！
Get your filthy hands off Princess Veronica!
女を人質に取るとは
なんて卑怯な…➡
You coward, taking a woman hostage!
じゃなくて バン よくやった！
I mean, well done, Ban!
(ﾊﾞﾝ)言うことさえ聞きゃ
なんもしねぇよ｡➡
As long as you do what I say, I won't hurt her.
First, return Cap'n back to normal.
Second, release the Princess from that ball.
まず 団ちょを元に戻して
その玉から 姫さんを出せ｡➡
そうすりゃ 女は返してやるぜ｡
Once that's done, I'll return her to you.
ザシュ ザシュ！
(ﾊﾞﾝ)ぐわっ！ てめぇ… ジャレコ！
You... Jaleco?!
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)うっ…｡
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)ベロニカ様！
Princess Veronica!
ジェリコだ｡
Jericho!
ふはははっ！ どうやら
いよいよ 主役の出番ってわけか｡
Looks like it's finally time for the main character to shine!
ホークちゃん？
くらえ！
Hawk?
Eat this! Rolling Ham Dash!
ローリング ハム･アタ～ック！
パチン
ぎゃあ～！
Hawk!
ホークちゃん！
We've completed all our objectives.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)目的は 全て達成しました｡➡
Sir Griamor, please release your power, if you'd be so kind.
グリアモール殿
魔力の解除を お願いいたします｡
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)うむ｡
あっ… きゃあ！
Here, Princess Elizabeth.
さあ お手をどうぞ｡
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)待ちな｡➡
Hold on.
I appreciate the assistance.
協力は感謝する｡
だが エリーは 私が連れて帰るよ｡
However, I will be taking Ellie back with me.
Your...
あんたたちの…
ヘンドリクセンの目的は➡
Hendriksen's objective was just to capture Meliodas and his sword, wasn't it?
あくまで
メリオダスと その剣だろ？
あっ！
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)き… 貴様！
You...!
Please be obedient and hand over Princess Elizabeth.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)おとなしく エリザベス様を
こちらへ渡しなさい｡
If not...
さもなくば…｡
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)はっ｡
I will not allow such insolence against Princess Veronica!
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)ベロニカ様への暴言は
この俺が許さん｡
Well done!
よくやった！
何を企んでいるかは知らんが➡
I don't know what you and Hendriksen are up to,
ヘンドリクセンともども 貴様らを
軍法会議にかける必要が➡
but you are to be tried in a court-martial!
あるようだな｡
ん… くっ！
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)あっ！
待つんだ エリー！ エリー！
Wait, Ellie!
Ellie!
I... can't believe in you anymore, Veronica!
≪もう
ベロニカ姉様なんて 信じない！≫
ん？ エ… エリザベスちゃん？
Elizabeth?
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)私たちも
王女様を捕まえる手伝いを➡
Shall we lend a hand in capturing the princess?
いたしましょうか？
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)いらぬ世話だ｡➡
No need.
You just stay there and make peace with your fate.
お前たちは
己の行く末を案じていろ｡
That's unfortunate.
それは残念です｡
まあ 回収できさえすれば➡
You see, our orders were to
retrieve the princess. Dead or alive.
最悪 死体でも
かまわないとのことでしたから｡
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)はっ… ベロニカ様～！
Princess Veronica!
ドオォーーン！
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)ベロニカ様～～‼
エリザベスちゃ～ん！
Princess Veronica!
Elizabeth?!
ベロニカ… 姉様？
Veronica...
うそ… どうして？
No... Why?
ベロニカ姉様 起きて｡
Veronica!
Wake up...
Please!
お願い 目を覚まして！
Open your eyes!
エリー？
ここに… エリーはここに｡
Ellie...
I-I'm here. Ellie's right here!
ケガは… ない？
Are you... unharmed?
I'm fine... because you protected me.
姉様が
私を かばってくれたから…｡
You've always... had a knack for getting into trouble...
あんたは
昔っから 危なっかしいから➡
私が かばって… やんないとね｡
So I... have to protect you... all the time...
うん… 二人で
お城を抜け出したときも…｡
Yeah... Just like when we snuck out of the castle.
私をかばって
大ケガをされたのは姉様なのに➡
You protected me... and ended up getting seriously injured...
All I could do was cry. And even then,
you were able to help and comfort me.
泣いてばかりいる私を
ずっと慰めてくれた｡
All the while ignoring your own pain.
ケガの痛みを ずっと我慢して…｡
だったかね…｡
I remember that...
I was really happy.
私 本当にうれしかったの｡
自分が 父上や姉様とは➡
You still cared about me even though I wasn't related to you or Father by blood.
なんの血のつながりもないことは
知ってたから…｡
だから… だから！ はっ｡
That's why...
Ellie...
エリー
関係ないんだよ そんなもの｡
It doesn't matter...
if we're not related.
I'm so sorry!
ごめんなさい！
さっきは あんなこと…➡
For what I said back then... That I hated you...
姉様のことを嫌いだなんて 私…｡
I... I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい！
大好き… だよ エリー｡
I... love you... Ellie...
私も… 私だって！
Me too... I love you.
I know...
分かってる 姉妹だもんね｡➡
We're sisters, after all.
グリアモール｡
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)はい｡
Griamor.
Yes!
This is my last order.
(ﾍﾞﾛﾆｶ)最後の命令だ｡
エリザベスを… 守って｡
Please protect Elizabeth...
Your last? Please, don't say such a thing!
最後だなんて
どうか そんなこと… はっ！
あっ… 姉様？
Veronica?
(ｸﾞﾘｱﾓｰﾙ)ベロニカ… 様…｡➡
Princess... Veronica?
うおぉ～～‼
Any moment now...
そろそろよ｡
何が？➡
What?
うわっ！
平静さを失い魔力が不安定になる｡
He lost his composure,
so his power became unstable.
My power, Killer Mine,
surrounds this area completely.
(ｷﾞｰﾗ)周囲３６０度の地中に➡
あらかじめ仕掛けておいて
正解でしたわ ｢キラーマイン｣｡
Looks like I made the right
decision to deploy it preemptively.
You swine bastards!
この豚畜生どもが～！
You b—
きさ…｡
プギャッ！
いいのか？ 聖騎士長の息子だぞ｡
Are you sure about this?
He's the son of the Great Holy Knight.
七つの大罪に襲われ
ベロニカ王女と共に➡
"Griamor and Princess Veronica were attacked by the Seven Deadly Sins and died unexpectedly,"
非業の死を遂げた…
それで十分でしょう？
should suffice, don't you think?
What a crazy woman.
(ｼﾞｪﾘｺ)おっかねぇ女｡
さあ エリザベス王女
我らと参りましょう｡
Now, Princess Elizabeth.
If you would, please come with us.
We ask that you don't put up a pointless show of resistance.
無駄な抵抗などされぬよう
協力を お願いします｡
ベロニカ姉様～！ ああっ あぁ…｡
Veronica!
お願い… 助けて メリオダス様…｡
Please, help me, Lord Meliodas!
No use calling for your hero now. He's sealed within that stone.
呼んでも 石の中の英雄は
助けになど来ませんよ｡ さっ｡
Now—
Meliodas!
メリオダス～～‼
Cap'n?!
団ちょ？ いや 違う｡
Wait, no... This feeling.
この感じ… まさか！
It can't be...
We're going back and forth on a dead-end street, yo
ittari kitari de ikidomari yo
mihatenu yume wa kori gori kori gori yo
This abandoned dream is a bitter experience, yo
After all, this world we live in is transient, yo
shosen konoyo wa ukiyo no sekai
Open up and defy them all to find high spirits, yo
hirakinaoreba NORINORINORINORI yo
High spirits, yo!
NORINORI yo
Throw in the firewood to reignite
maki wo kubero tayasu na sono hi wo
Your blazing passion before it goes out
tsuki ugokasu MONO wa sou kandou sa
The future will be fine as long as it shines brightly
mirai wa tada kagayaite kurete ireba ii’nda
We switched our intense rampage on
bokura wa Gan Gan abare MO-DO
Making seven sounds of thunder
todorokasu Boom Boom nanatsu no oto
Heading toward an ever-bright tomorrow
Rin Rin hikaru ashita e to susumou
We're ready to shoot the place up
bokura wa Bang Bang HAJI ke MO-DO
Jumping here and there as we go
buttobasu Ran Dom SUTAIRU de ikou yo
Shining through like a diamond
Bling Bling hikaru DAIYAMONDO
Let's go, now we can fly high
iku ze Now we can fly high
Next Episode's Report
バイゼル喧嘩祭りも混乱の極み｡
The Byzel Fight Festival has become total chaos!
聖騎士 対 七つの大罪の戦いは
過激にヒートアップ！
The battle between the Holy Knights and the
Seven Deadly Sins is reaching the boiling point!
それでは 私ラブヘルムも
退避したいと思います｡➡
Even I, Love♡Helm, believe it's time to retreat!
さようなら～！ ああっ！
I bid you farewell!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)な～んちゃって｡
ラブリー審判 ラブヘルムとは➡
Just kidding.
The lovely referee Love♡Helm was just a temporary alias.
仮の姿｡ その実体は➡
His true identity is the evil Cardinal, Helbram!
悪の枢機卿 ヘルブラム｡
あっ… あれ!?
H-Huh?!
次回 『七つの大罪』 ｢破壊の使途｣｡
Next time, on The Seven Deadly Sins: "Disciple of Destruction."
Stayed tuned for my big debut!
(ﾍﾙﾌﾞﾗﾑ)
俺っちの大活躍に 乞うご期待｡
Episode 13
Disciple of Destruction
アメリカ･ニューヨーク市警の警官
２人が
男に銃で撃たれ死亡した｡
男は銃で自殺したが､
事件の前､インターネット上で